EPISODE 1
REIGN OF RENZONG
IN THE NORTHERN SONG DYNASTY
Boss, give me one that's fresh and hot.
It smells pretty good.
BIANJING
Just a moment.
- Alright, I'll take those then.
- Okay.
Sesame oil. Top-quality sesame oil.
- Steamed buns.
- Sesame oil.
Nice and hot.
Peanut cake.
Come take a look.
Let's get this one.
- Nice and hot.
- Here you go.
PAN RESTAURANT
- Welcome!
- They have a new owner now.
- Does Pan Restaurant sell Penglai Chun?
- Yes, it does.
When it comes to good wine,
the Meishou
from Baifan Restaurant is the best.
Let's give it a try.
Let's go.
Waiter, table for three.
Three gentlemen, please come.
I can't feel my arms with you there.
Get up.
MADAM LI
ELDEST DAUGHTER, SHOUHUA
Come on. Brush your teeth.
Mom is really stingy.
Why not hire a sedan chair
to go into the city?
It's both convenient and respectable.
So noisy.
You're stepping on me.
FIFTH DAUGHTER, LESHAN
- Stop it. The vehicle is shaking.
- Quick.
Oil spilled out.
- Okay.
- You.
Mom.
Stop fooling around. Hurry.
There's hair oil left.
- Come on.
- Only quiet when you're all asleep.
- She's stepping on me.
- Don't move.
Don't mention those darn people anymore.
In broad daylight,
they start daydreaming.
They ask for 120 coins right off the bat.
A hundred and twenty coins, seriously?
Later, when we arrive
at your second sister's house,
all the sedans
are yours to sit on if you like.
No wonder everyone says
Bianjing's splendor's
unrivaled in the world.
Sister,
look at that door.
They've even put up a decorative arch.
There are many ladies
with flowers in the hair on the pavilion.
Over here.
- Let me have a look.
- Careful with the oil.
- Your skirt.
- Be careful.
Can you be a bit more mature?
Pancakes.
Here, kind guest. Have one.
MADAM LIU, CHUNLAI
QIONGNU
PAN RESTAURANT
Sis.
Look over there.
Someone is gorgeously dressed.
Isn't it new?
Can we wear something like that
in the future?
- Ask Mother.
- Let's settle down in Bianjing first.
Then, I will find each of you
a good husband.
I will have no regrets after that.
CHAI AN
- LIANG JUNQING
- My lord.
Enjoy your meal, my lord.
I'll be right outside.
Just call if you need anything.
In this city, only Master Chai has wealth
worth 10,000 strings of coin.
In the blink of an eye,
he took over such a large shop.
But I heard the old owner has suffered
great losses for three consecutive years.
Lost a lot of wealth.
You faint-hearted ones.
What kind of person is Master Chai?
News was shared from the Palace.
Whoever takes on the 20,000-gold
liquor taxes from Pan Restaurant
will be authorized to open
1,000 liquor stores.
You'll never need to worry about cash
as it flows in like water.
That'd be fantastic.
Ordinary people might never get the news.
Even if they knew,
who would have the nerve to execute?
Right.
Are you afraid of the cold?
The windows are all shut,
yet you're not taking it off.
You're not a lady.
A grown man going out wearing this?
I was stung by a bee yesterday
and got such a big swelling.
I don't want to ruin the view.
I am ashamed.
I drank too much last night
and took a tumble.
Scared of being mocked
for being drunk.
I hope you all will forgive me for this.
No worries.
Everyone, out.
Out!
I…
Put it down.
Such a big bee.
- Was it your wife again?
- No, no.
I was drunk last night
and got a bit intimate with the maid.
FAN LIANGHAN
My lady was angry, and we argued.
I fell off the bed. But it's alright.
You're so useless.
- Let's go.
- Where to?
I must personally meet your shrewish wife.
Absolutely not, if you provoke her,
she might just eat you up.
FAN’S MANSION
What bad timing.
Our master and mistress
are away for the summer holidays.
They are not at home.
Please inform your master
that his wife's family
has traveled far from Luoyang to visit.
He has gone to meet friends.
Then, when will he be back?
At noon, he is usually at Sang's house.
Night entertainment after that.
We wouldn't know when he will be back.
- What's the matter?
- What does she mean?
Then, please take the trouble to go again
and tell our second lady
to come out and greet.
She's gone to Xiangguo Temple
for charity events.
Sorry for the trouble, madam.
Please come again another day.
Alright. Heading back.
Sweep this away. How unpleasant to see.
Madam, what are you doing?
Not yesterday,
nor tomorrow.
Such a coincidence.
We just arrived and everyone is out.
It seems my mail was addressed to a dog.
Madam,
please don't be mad.
They are not at home, really.
Go back and tell your master.
When my second girl was back home,
we always greeted distant guests
with proper manners.
We never let them linger at the door,
waiting without even a cup of tea.
This is nonsense.
Our girl joined the Fan family
less than two years ago.
She now turned her back
on her widowed mother and sisters.
This is not marriage.
This is uncivilized downgrading
to savages.
As for that one,
with an evil heart and rotten guts,
I'll just assume I was blind
and raised them for nothing.
You just go back and tell her.
Even if I have to beg for food
from now on,
I will never come here,
at the doorstep of the Fan family.
Let's go.
- But…
- No need.
- What?
- Let's go.
FAN’S MANSION
SECOND DAUGHTER, FUHUI
Mother.
It's pitiful.
Pity for my…
200 strings dowry.
Two hundred strings?
FAN'S MANSION
It's getting dark.
Time to rest.
You want to stay over?
- Take off your clothes.
- My lord.
I mean, I want to borrow your clothes.
Mother, don't be angry.
Second sister may have her own concerns.
Mother, a decoction to calm your nerves.
Have some at least.
Raised for nothing.
Really. Nothing.
Terribly ungrateful.
A beast without gratitude.
Come.
Take these 200 coins.
Buy some donkey meat pastries,
some mung bean soup,
and some grass jelly to cool off.
I am afraid Mom has no appetite.
That stove looks rather clean to me.
Please also borrow some rice.
Ask Chunlai to make some rice porridge.
We'll settle
the fire-lighting fee tomorrow.
Do you know the way?
Mother has a picky taste.
You can go to Zhang's for pastries,
right across the street.
Turn right and keep going
until you get to Second Street.
With another hundred steps,
you'll see Wang's fish noodle stall.
On the east side of the stall,
there is a Lucky Shoe Store.
Next to it, Lin family's grass jelly
has a long queue. Buy from there.
I wasn't able to see clear
during the bumpy ride.
But thank you, my fourth lady.
You have a good memory.
I'll go then.
Mother.
It's cold.
Where is third lady?
They said Master Chai
invited quite a few people over,
playing and singing.
The noise is incessant.
Later on, he was too drunk to walk.
He had to be carried back.
What about my husband?
The young master stayed with a girl
in the side chamber.
That naughty piece of shit.
My lady.
Fan Lianghan, you did take a vow.
Can't believe such a violent wife
is from the Li family of Luoyang.
Your late father
must be restless in his grave.
A saying goes,
"The violent one is heartless.
The ugly one envies."
Five daughters from Luoyang Li family
are all famous for beauty.
You are not ugly or heartless.
Why so jealous?
It should be between you two.
I never intended to do this.
But you hit and scold your husband,
making domestic issues known all over.
He is my cousin. I can't just ignore it.
Marrying a good husband
should be a great thing in life.
I advise you, sister-in-law.
From now on, put away
this envy for favor and vanity.
Don't break the seven rules for divorce
out of temper and jealousy.
Ending up a divorced and discarded woman
will bring disgrace to your Li family.
Come out!
Cousin, is that all?
If Auntie hasn't begged me to,
I won't bother with your trivial matters.
You two are never at peace.
If she makes one mistake, you make nine.
Her fierce and jealous nature,
I bet you've driven her to it.
Fan Lianghan,
if you dare fool around outside again
and word gets back to me,
you'll get a hundred flogging.
If you die, fine.
Cousin,
I just look and talk about it.
I've never been serious about it.
My wife is too fierce.
Whenever a mosquito flies by,
she has to catch it to check the gender.
- Cousin.
- You're driving me crazy.
I'll walk around. Do not follow.
Go back.
From now on, put away
this envy for favor and vanity.
Don't break the seven rules for divorce
out of temper and jealousy.
Ending up a divorced
and discarded woman
will bring disgrace to your Li family.
Second sister.
Kneel.
In front of the sisters,
share your thoughts.
Make it clear.
Madam.
Second lady has suffered a lot.
Second sister.
When I first joined the Fan family,
I was also favored by Mother-in-law.
We were a harmonious couple.
But as time went by,
I found out Fan's eldest son
was soft-hearted.
Those companions in the parlor.
Strange girls playing flute and lute.
Everyone was his favorite.
Whoever cries about life in front of him,
he would cry along with them.
Often with red and swollen eyes,
he came back with an empty purse.
The elders pity their son.
Told him off a few of times,
but he never changed.
They just gave up on him.
What is this?
But it is not true if you say
he treats me poorly.
The beaded treasures
and curios in my room,
the royal girls might not have them.
I wanted to learn to play Dakyu.
He helped me a lot
by organizing teams and clubs.
In March, he took me to play water swings.
He fell down from a high place,
almost losing his life,
all for me and my smile.
Perhaps I am too jealous
to be a virtuous wife.
Don't give me excuses.
I'm asking you.
What is this?
Chewing pebbles to overcome jealousy.
Mother.
I don't want to resort to violence.
A bad reputation spreads far and wide.
But I…
can never change it.
Oh, Fuhui.
Second sister is afraid of being a burden
on the Li family, on us.
That's why she refused to meet us today.
What are you talking about?
No, it is true.
Six fierce ladies of the Li Family
scared off all the matchmakers in Luoyang.
If word spread in Bianjing
about another envious Li's girl,
it'll be unbearably worse.
I thought it was a big deal,
like the end of the world.
Among these five girls,
you are the most alike
to your weakling muddle-headed father.
Mother, you don't want me to bear it?
Enduring is a temporary approach.
But we are here now.
We will make him change
instead of you tolerating everything.
Third sister means that
looking back, families were ruined
by too much drink,
lust, wealth, and anger.
Excessive drinking and lust
lead to gossip and quarrels,
even to physical injuries and murder.
There are countless cases in the world.
Brother-in-law is young and impetuous.
It is good for him to cultivate morals
and avoid disputes.
If you are afraid of the gossip
and indulge him blindly,
it will lead to trouble in the future.
That is not virtuous after all.
Then, sister, what should I do?
Tackling the root of the problem
is not difficult.
I'm afraid that second sister won't do it.
I will.
As long as it is good for him,
I will do anything.
Then, no problem.
If you follow my advice,
within half a year,
if you tell him to go east,
he will never go west.
Tell him to hold the plow,
he won't climb the ladder.
He will become a compliant
and obedient husband.
No, he will be a down-to-earth husband
who earnestly mends his ways.
All the same.
Second sister,
with your beauty and virtue,
he should do nothing but cherish you.
If I were you, I'd beat him up and see
what's in his silly brain.
Starting from today,
he shall see the magic of our third lady.
FAN'S MANSION
My lord. My lord.
My lord.
The lady left a message.
Your mother-in-law and sisters
have arrived in Bianjing.
Today they want to visit our silk store
to pick some fabric.
My lord, please stay at home
and prepare a good banquet.
What did you just say? Say it again.
Fan Lianghan.
Cousin, you are here.
Didn't you say yesterday,
the Zhuang's new store has taken
a lot of your customers?
I am free today. I can go with you.
Let's see what tricks
they are playing secretly.
Get up.
Behave yourself. Have you forgotten
what I told you some days ago?
Cousin.
My wife is not at home today.
My lord.
The lady has returned.
Hurry. Go.
Quick. Hurry up.
Go, go, go.
There's no time.
It's too late. The lady has returned.
Where can I hide?
The lady has returned.
Here.
Get out.
No.
Cousin.
- Cousin, save me.
- Get up.
- Save me, please.
- Stand up.
Don't embarrass me.
My dear,
I have something important to tell you.
This is the symptom of a migraine.
Why is the doctor not here yet?
The doctor is informed
and will be here soon.
My lord, please bear it a bit.
Hurry up.
- My lady.
- What happened?
It hurts terribly, my lady.
Help!
It hurts.
Pain.
My lady.
You must've been drinking too much.
Returned at night
and caught in the wind again.
People often get sick by doing that.
Fortunately, it is not difficult to cure.
No need for a doctor. I can treat it.
I wonder,
what kind of treatment are you preparing?
Coming.
My lady, the medicine is here.
Come, my lord.
I will personally attend to you.
Cousin Chai, rest assured.
Once this medicine is taken,
it will cure all ailments.
I've never heard of a medicine
that cures all diseases in this world.
Is this really right?
Indeed. Come on. Drink this first.
What is this taste?
My lord, this is a local remedy.
Boy's urine. Specifically
for treating chills, fever, and headaches.
Just bear with it.
Hurry over and serve the lord.
Go quickly.
Come.
If the lord refuses to take the medicine,
I wonder, are you faking the pain?
- No.
- Not drinking?
I'll drink.
Here.
Blame yourself for that.
Finish it all.
- It will all be fine.
- Who's there?
Alright,
just spit it out and you'll be fine.
Boy's urine?
Third sister, is it really boy's urine?
Of course not.
It's just vinegar with water.
Plus five spoons salt, six spoons
soy sauce, and three sugars.
Among our five sisters,
you are the most mischievous one.
Almost scared my brother-in-law to death.
Third sister is always clever and crafty.
If you ask me,
this libertine's problem
is the easiest to fix.
Just break his legs.
Tie him to the second sister's bedpost,
and he'll behave.
Just eat.
In Bianjing, I am alone and with no help.
Now, mother and sisters came.
You are my core and support.
It feels good.
Two gentlemen.
Young master is at the study.
This way, please.
Let's go.
Wait.
Who is inside the pavilion?
- Our young lady's family came to visit.
- Let me see.
Those are Fan's beautiful cousins.
They came to the capital.
I heard Fan praised them a lot,
saying they have unmatched beauty.
As if they are goddesses
living in seclusion.
Here, take a look.
That's rare.
I think we should go and pay a visit.
Pay a visit.
Absolutely not, sir.
Won't make it hard for you.
Just have a look.
Just a quick glance.
No, please. You can't do it.
Here, let me pour you a little more.
From such a distance,
we can't see their faces clearly.
Who knows if they are beautiful or not?
Yes, two gentlemen.
You can't get any closer.
If we get caught
for peeking at the ladies,
not just us,
the young master would be in trouble.
Quiet down.
I have an idea.
This is unacceptable.
I visit here often.
Sooner or later, I will meet the ladies.
If you make a fuss,
I'll say you instigated it.
I…
I have prepared the rooms.
Why don't you stay?
Help me talk to Mom, please?
Here, it is Fan's Mansion, not Li's.
It is not proper for you unmarried sisters
to stay long and treat
this as your original house.
That will be a joke for all.
Moreover, if relatives from
the maternal home stay long at your place,
the Fan family will later
look down on you.
What?
Why are you laughing without reason?
A few days ago, I saw a joke in a book.
It's funny but rather vulgar.
I'm afraid to offend my sisters.
I'll just keep it to myself
and enjoy it alone.
I know you.
If you don't say it, you will get gloomy.
Get it off your chest.
- Share it now.
- Do tell.
Well, then. I'll start.
In the grand scheme of things,
nothing's more paltry than ants and flies.
One day, however, they started to argue.
The ant said, "Though I am small,
there's a sense of sovereignty
and servitude in my behavior.
When I find food,
I will surely share with others.
As for loyalty and filial piety,
I shall take the lead."
The fly was not convinced.
"That's all well, but none enjoys as I do.
In the imperial palaces and gardens,
the mansions of the wealthy,
and during grand feasts,
I can enter and roam at will
and enjoy freely.
I should be the leader."
Upon hearing this, the mosquito
expressed its dissent.
"Though you two speak of loyalty,
filial piety, and wealth,
none of you lives as joyfully
and freely as I do."
How so?
"In the dead of night, when all is still,
within the fragrant lady's quarters,
I am free to come and go.
Regardless of her status being
a princess or a noble lady,
a heroine or a goddess,
I only choose the sweetest
and most delicate spots to feast upon
and only stop when I am fully satisfied."
Hearing this, the ant and the fly
were furious.
"Look at you, with your sharp snout.
Such lechery."
How dare you?
Do you know who my uncle is?
Even if I took you as a concubine,
it'd be a miracle for your family.
Mess with me,
you and the Li family will be in trouble.
Scoundrel.
- Take my shovel.
- Fifth sister.
You.
Help.
You blind hedonist, shameless beast!
How dare you even dream
of taking my sister.
So covetous of the prosperity
for my family,
why don't you come over and kowtow to me?
If you don't shut your foul mouth
and take back your frivolous talks,
watch out for my shovel.
It will mash up your wolfish heart.
I'll pull out your filthy intestines
and feed you with firecrackers.
You'll never reincarnate after death.
Fifth sister, please stay calm.
- You…
- What?
Remember.
It is the third lady of Li
who beats you today.
Nothing to do with anyone else.
You disguised as maids in broad daylight,
peeking at ladies.
Bullied with borrowed power,
a fox masquerading as a tiger.
Despicable and lowly,
shameless and heartless.
If you don't accept this, go
to the Bureau for Letters to talk it out.
Even if your uncle is some dragon king
or god of the mountains,
the laws of Song still prevail.
The imperial censors in the city
will not tolerate it.
Certainly, they will inquire about
allowing his nephew's misconduct.
I want to see how you can escape that.
I won't dare.
My fault.
Sorry for the interruption, ladies.
Who let them in? Seize them!
They love to dress as women, don't they?
We have time for that.
- Exactly.
- Guards, take them away.
Mother.
- Very well.
- Mother.
Mother, look at her,
causing trouble again.
Big sister.
No nonsense.
If the host recognizes them,
they'll be guests.
If not, they are lascivious thieves.
Even if you beat them to death,
no one would hold you accountable.
Alright. Let's go back.
Return to the inn soon.
Cousin.
- Cousin.
- Speak properly.
What are you ranting about?
It's rather disgusting.
Cousin.
My mother-in-law and her daughters
have all come to Bianjing.
How can I survive in the future?
The Li families are all women.
Just take good care of them.
What're you talking about?
Cousin, you don't know.
Save me, Fan.
- Save me.
- Save me, Fan.
In the garden.
You have offended my wife?
My wife hit you?
You're going to get me killed.
No, we won't dare.
- Not your wife.
- It was a young lady with a nice voice.
Very fierce, quite scary.
There's also a scourge.
She hit me like this.
- Beating me without warning.
- Yes.
Her curses were terrible.
Extremely terrible.
I thought young ladies were shy
and wouldn't do anything
if they noticed us.
Who would have thought?
This is not surprising.
The Li family in Luoyang
had many hectares of good farmland.
Unfortunately,
my father-in-law passed away early.
The son died prematurely too.
In this house, where masculinity
ended, if the woman is weak,
they won't be able to protect
their family property.
That's right.
They also said
- the ones you associate with are evil too.
- Right.
Now, they'll hit once they see one.
- No matter if it is two or a dozen.
- Yes.
- Especially Mr. Chai.
- Right.
Still trying to provoke me with lies?
I don't know her.
Why hit me without reason?
She said you're the one instigating Fan
to reinforce the male authority.
On normal days,
too proud to see the dust beneath.
The most arrogant and rude one.
Mr. Chai, you must be careful.
That one who did the beating
must be the fifth lady.
The one who did the talking
must be the third lady.
The fifth lady smiles
at everyone she meets.
But her mother and elder sisters
can never be dishonored in front of her.
It's your fault for being indecent.
- I made a mistake.
- The third lady who fed you with vinegar.
She wants to get even with me.
Good.
I look forward to the challenge.
Cousin, you mustn't go. It's a suicide.
- Don't go.
- Mr. Chai.
- Stop him.
Quick, stop him.
Mother.
Stay a little longer.
I can come again next time.
Stay for a few more days.
Mother.
Third sister.
You.
No, sis, you can't do it.
Mr. Liang.
Are you alright?
I can see many birds around me.
You're so silly. Why didn't you dodge?
Who is playing cuju over there?
Get up quickly.
My name is Chai An.
I am a friend of this house.
The ball slipped away.
I should be more careful.
I ask for Lady Li
and the other ladies' forgiveness.
If I broke anything,
I will pay for it at double the price.
- Who is the man playing cuju…
- Mother-in-law.
- …with third sister?
- My lady.
- Sisters-in-law.
- I don't know.
Mr. Chai's my cousin. He doesn't know
they were in the garden.
He showed off but people got hurt.
It's my fault for not explaining.
It was completely unintentional.
Blame me. It's all my fault.
Mother.
The Chai and Fan families
share a deep friendship.
Mr. Chai
is a frequent visitor in our home.
Usually, he is the most courteous one.
He certainly
didn't mean to offend the ladies.
Shall we be over with it, for me?
This gentleman is quite handsome.
He brings joy at first sight.
Are you…?
Never mind.
Sure, all is good.
Then we shall leave now.
Let me show you the way.
Let's go.
That was close. Dodged a bullet.
You deserved it. This concubine nonsense.
If you sincerely apologize,
she won't be that angry.
It's her.
Such a refreshing and stunning lady.
She is the one and only in Bianjing.
You deserved that hit from the ball.
Please return the hairpin comb to my lady.
Come try it.
That gentleman playing cuju
has a good demeanor.
He's much different from
the previous two with their sneaky looks.
Is he married?
When you approached the city,
did you see the gardens on the outskirts?
Yes.
One after another,
stretching as far as the eye can see.
It all belongs to his family?
The Chai family acquired a lot of land
on the outskirts of the city early on.
They hired skilled people
to plant vegetables widely.
Even during the cold winter,
fresh chive shoots and purslanes
are never short of supply.
One acre of the garden
is worth ten acres of farmland.
One can tell the wealth of his family
without asking.
It's nothing special to own land.
We also have good fields in Luoyang.
Mother, think about it.
Bianjing has all the princes,
dukes, ministers, and dignitaries.
How do they let ordinary people
have good benefits?
What I will be sharing today,
sisters, just take it as a joke.
Nobody should take it seriously.
It is said that Emperor Taizu,
during his humble beginnings,
received kindness
from Emperor Shizong of the Great Zhou.
In the end,
the Zhao family took their empire.
It's inevitable they feel guilt towards
Chai family descendants.
Rumors say that Emperor Shizong of Zhou
had seven sons.
Some died early.
Some had unknown whereabouts.
Some adopted by prominent officials
under Emperor Taizu's instruction.
Their surnames were changed to Pan and Lu.
Back to now,
after generations of his family,
it is hard to tell the truth.
I've only heard he spoke once
carelessly after drinking.
The family still offered incense
to the cinnabar edict.
- Really?
- Oh my goodness.
Grandma often said
the Fan family is considered wealthy.
But it is nothing
compared to their family.
Thanks to the Chai family's consideration
of old sentiments, they look after us.
Although he tends to meddle too much,
he is the only one sincerely
helping my husband
in his career and life.
In that case,
Master Chai must already
have a marriage arranged.
He is a man with his own ideas.
Ordinary women do not catch his eye.
I think, sooner or later,
he will marry a noble woman.
All that chatter.
If he doesn't marry my dear daughters,
who cares about his future bride.
It has nothing to do
with our family, right?
Had I known this,
I should've taught him a lesson earlier.
Ask him to pay the head comb.
Wasted good intentions.
Mother, I've found a good house agent
to rent a quiet residence
near the Fan's Mansion.
Shall we go and check on the house?
I still have important things
to take care of.
Third daughter, you come with me.
Okay.
Eldest daughter, Shouhua.
This is my third daughter, Kangning.
This one
is my fourth daughter, Haode.
And this
is my youngest fifth daughter, Leshan.
Alright.
Ms. Liu,
please don't forget to remind me later.
After offering the incense,
pack up all the portraits to take back.
Okay.
Bodhisattva, I offer you incense.
Bodhisattva.
Devout woman here, sincerely praying.
May my daughter's marriage be smooth.
The fourth and fifth daughters can wait.
But the eldest, Shouhua,
widowed at a young age,
wasting her youth.
And the third daughter, Kangning,
with a fierce temperament,
finding her a partner isn't easy.
They really can't wait any longer.
I don't ask for a son-in-law
to be very wealthy or noble.
But I wish my daughter
will find a good man
to support her all her life.
I pray for the Bodhisattva's blessing
for mother's and sisters' health
for our family
to have a roof over our heads
and a place to stand our ground.
Live in peace with simple tea and meals.
These are all my wishes.
Thinking only of her own daughters,
in this world, who will pity me?
They have suffered a lot
since they were young.
So, I hope for the rest of their lives,
they can find good husbands
and live simple and harmonious lives.
- Thief! Mom.
- Don't run.
- He took our things.
- Thief.
- Stop the thief.
Catch the thief!
Slow down, Mother.
- Mother.
- Take it slow.
Is it because you know my daughters
can't get married?
- Don't move.
- I met respectable families.
- I'll hit you.
- Mother.
- Alright.
- Don't be angry with him.
Mother, calm down, please.
How can there be
such a vulgar woman in the world?
What kind of place is this
to tolerate her nonsense?
She keeps saying
she is marrying off her daughter.
A daughter of such a family,
who would dare to propose to her?
I can't stand it here.
It is filled with filthy noise.
- Let's go inside.
- Okay.
- Take it easy.
- My daughters can't get married.
- It's on you.
- Mother, stop.
Madam, please spare me.
I have a docile and sensible daughter.
She is not married because we are poor.
I fear she will grow old and die at home.
Out of desperation, I resorted to theft.
I beg you, madam, to be generous.
Spare me this once.
I will never do it again.
- I am begging you.
- A girl from a poor family.
To be old and unmarried,
that is pitiful indeed.
Kind madam,
please have mercy and spare him.
Please spare him for once.
Please spare him.
Alright. I won't pursue this any further.
- I'll let you go.
- Merciful indeed.
- Let him go.
- Thank you, madam.
- Wait a moment.
- Good people are sure to be rewarded.
Here, I give this to you.
Consider it a good deed for myself.
Also, as a contribution
to your daughter's dowry.
Thank you, madam.
- No need to thank me.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
The matter is settled.
All is fine. Let's leave.
Let's go.
You may leave.
Thank you.
How has this practice of expensive dowries
in Bianjing evolved to this point?
Daughters of the poor can't get married.
You are not locals, right?
- Yes.
- You may not be aware.
In Bianjing,
wealth is most important in a wife.
The families that have daughters
all start saving the dowry early.
Hope the prep helps when
the daughter is the age for marriage.
You mentioned having daughters.
I wonder how many young ladies you have.
Five of them.
Four.
Only one has been married off.
Pardon my frankness,
but allow me to add this.
People said, "Thieves won't visit
the house with five daughters."
Since you have five daughters,
the dowries required for their marriages
must amount to hundreds of millions.
I'm afraid when the day comes,
even thieves will look around.
Hundreds of millions?
With only these ordinary assets,
even the bodhisattvas wouldn't notice.
With such stinginess, madam,
it'll be hard for your daughters
to get married.
You might as well
keep all these for yourself.
You scoundrel.
You old coffin.
Blind to good intentions, infuriating!
- Who are you talking about?
- Mother, it's alright now.
- Don't you have…
- Mother.
- Madam.
- Quick. Pinch her.
- Okay.
- Pinch her.
- Hit the acupoint.
Subtitle translation by: Wenlong Zhong